{
    "subject": "resource/International_Surf_Lifesaving_Association",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Organization",
    "human_readable": "The International Surf Lifesaving Association is an organization.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.979772686958313,
            "question": "What type of organization is the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9679940938949585,
            "question": "Is the International Surf Lifesaving Association a governmental or non-governmental organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9585220217704773,
            "question": "What does the International Surf Lifesaving Association do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9459156394004822,
            "question": "What countries are involved in the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9220795035362244,
            "question": "What is the mission statement of the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9168589115142822,
            "question": "Are there any specific events or competitions organized by the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8859507441520691,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges faced by the International Surf Lifesaving Association?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.830754816532135,
            "question": "How does the International Surf Lifesaving Association promote water safety?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8116484880447388,
            "question": "Does the International Surf Lifesaving Association provide training or certification programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649925351142883,
            "question": "Does the International Surf Lifesaving Association have any regional chapters or branches?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The International Surf Lifesaving Association is an organization.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3128_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the International Surf Lifesaving Association provide training or certification programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3128_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the International Surf Lifesaving Association promote water safety?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3128_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges faced by the International Surf Lifesaving Association?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3128_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3128_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents clearly state that the International Surf Lifesaving Association (ISLA) is an international organization, a non-profit organization, and a charity. Therefore, it can be inferred that ISLA is indeed an organization."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents describe the International Surf Lifesaving Association (ISLA) as an international organization that advances professional lifesaving development and provides various services related to aquatic safety. Therefore, it supports the statement that ISLA is an organization."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}